Bullshit.
It is this friggin' wide.
And it's periodic.
Bull. Shit.
Show me.
Something terrestrial, gotta be.
Bouncing off the moon.
Gee. I never thought to check that.
Look at that slope, man.
You could ski down that thing.
It is drifting.
Look here. Zoom in. Zoom in.
See that variation?
And look. This gap here?
This is where it stops, then starts over.
-It repeats?
-Every 78 seconds.
The whole entire thing.
Three hours straight, and no end in sight.
It can't be.
It's gotta be something
bouncing off the... off the...
It's not bouncing off the moon, Dave.
Well, maybe it's those Chatty Cathys
at the Forest Service.
I hate those guys. Always on their radios,
talking about trees.
Dave, it's not Smokey Bear
we're picking up.
Look at that signal.
It's drifting.
What is it, then?
Looks like simple pulse-width modulation.
Old-school, like Morse code.
Maybe somehow,
it's the time signal out of Fort Collins.
-They use pulse-width modulation.
-It's not the atomic clock.
The atomic clock changes every minute
because it's a clock.
This is the same exact data
repeated every 78 seconds.
Plus, this is coming
from 600 light-years away.
This Morse code of yours
seems to be split four ways.
The pulses are of equal duration,
but they're positioned
across four different frequencies.
-Looks like a player piano.
-So not binary but base four.
Quaternary.
This won't be easy to crack.
No, no. If you look at this. Look at...
What do you think it says?
Maybe just,
"Hello. Hey, hey. We're out here."
What did we put on Voyagers 1 and 2?
Chuck Berry?
Maybe this is just
their version of "Johnny B. Goode."
Imagine the power it took to send it.
Megawatts?
Gigawatts?
And that's if it's pointed only at us.
Antenna the size of Africa.
-Mm-hmm.
-Bigger.
You go to all that trouble
to send a message,
it's gotta be more than just "hello."
And why make it hard to understand?
Quaternary?
That's like encryption.
Why would you bother to...
It's not quaternary.
I think I know what it is.
The twin moons hung low and full.
Two wine-green eyes
peering over the horizon
as if to steal a glimpse
into Lucasia's soul.
She paced the blood-soaked decks
of the Mercator,
looking for something, anything,
that might take her mind off Raban.
Ascending the forecastle, her gaze
lingered over a bare-chested young sailor.
On hands and knees he scrubbed,
his sinewy forearms stretched taut as he
washed away all trace of the day's fight.
With a languid nod...
...Lucasia bade him follow to her cabin.
Little did this callow deckhand know
that serving at his captain's pleasure
might take on such sweet meaning.
Or, regrettably,
that it would last but a single night.
Later, at four bells,
Lucasia stood by the mizzenmast.
Once again, she was alone.
She pulled her topcoat tighter,
fingering its coarse wool
as her thoughts flashed back to Raban.
It had been he who first wrapped
the coat around her,
whispering in her ear,
"May this keep you warm
in my absence, ma chérie."
With that, Raban, proud, haughty Raban,
mounted the plank and leaped from sight.
The am a ran thine
slips and closed over him,
leaving nary a ripple.
Aw...
Attention, lovers of
speculative historical romance literature,
best-selling author Carol Sturka
will now sign her new novel,
"Bloodsong of Wycaro,"
the fourth book in her
"Winds of Wycaro" trilogy.
"Why-car-oh," please!
It's "Winds of Why-car-oh!"
And Bloodsong is the best yet.
God, are you in for a treat.
Let's go sign books!
Raban is alive, right?
Maureen. You could read it.
Well, I will. Tonight.
I've already unplugged the phone.
Just, uh...
-Raban's not on the cover.
-No, he's not.
And he... he's never not been
on the cover, Carol.
If Raban doesn't come back...
...I'm done.
Come here.
Page 218.
-Okay. Thank you.
-Okay. Bye.
Thanks, Maureen.
-Okay, this is Olga.
-Hi. Hi, Olga.
Hi, Yvette!
Hi!
Love it.
-Happy reading.
-This is Nicky, with a pillow.
-Nicky with a... Oh, my gosh!
-I made it myself.
-Look at that. You made this?
-Yes.
This is Christine.
This is Paulina and support person.
-This is Carlotta.
-Hi.
Say, "Raban".
Raban.
When Raban and Eldgammel
fell in the cargo hold,
do you remember what it was loaded with?
Mandovian spice fruit.
Which Lucasia is...
Deathly allergic to!
-Oh, you guys run a fan club?
-Of course!
-Thank you so much!
-Thank you.
-Hi, Tanya.
-Hi!
-Are you excited?
-Yes.
-Hi, Yvonne.
-Hi.
I got two books, one for the tub.
This is a authentic cutlass
just like Raban's.
-Okay.
-Careful, it's really sharp.
Okay, so three things.
When finally are they
gonna make a "Wycaro" movie?
And please tell me it'll be in actual
theaters, not on the Lifetime Network.
You gotta get ILM to do the slips and,
otherwise it's just gonna look like merde,
pardon my French.
A small but very crucial point,
as a two-masted schooner, the Mercator
would not possess a mizzenmast. So...
Craig, I'm gonna need you
to put this back in the bag
before the store manager sees it.
-Oh.
-Right.
-Your humble servant.
-Thank you.
Oh, that's the one.
Thank you so much.
-We'll see you at the next one.
-Happy reading.
All right. All right.
Hi, ladies. I have us
going to the Hyatt Regency Dallas.
Hi. Yeah. Thanks, uh, perfect.
That was quite a send-off.
I'm sorry, should I know who you are?
Uh, depends.
You a big fan of mindless crap?
Morning, Doc.
Well, it certainly is.
-Hey, Mel.
-Hey.
Ooh, where'd those come from?
Yours truly.
Help yourself.
I think they're mostly glazed,
but one box ought to be sprinkled,
powdered and all that.
What did we do to deserve this?
Ah, my 14-year-old's selling 'em
for marching band.
Well, aren't you a good dad.
-What does she play?
-Trombone.
-Doctor D!
-Good evening.
Morning. Whatever.
-Look what Mel brought.
-Ooh, for us?
Yeah, please.
They got you two working late.
Yeah. I gotta gas a bunch of rats.
So, how goes the big project?
What have you heard?
I don't know. Things.
Well...
Our team's fairly certain
we've got a sequence
that encodes for a lysogenic virus.
But after eight whole months
of animal testing...
Macaques, rabbits, mice...
-Guinea pigs.
-Guinea pigs. Now rats.
No clinical signs whatsoever.
Put another way...
we got bubkes.
We got bubkes.
Okay, how do you wanna do this?
Uh, I can put 'em to sleep
if you wanna do the cardiac sticks.
I hate the cardiac sticks.
Well, you're more than welcome
to gas them.
I hate gassing them.
Might be in the wrong career.
All right, cardiac sticks it is.
Let's get it over with.
Uh-oh.
Check it out.
Oh, damn.
What do you figure happened there?
I don't know.
He's looking pretty dead to me.
You got a heartbeat?
I can't feel jack shit in these gloves.
Huh.
Huh, what?
He's absolutely got a heartbeat.
A strong one. Just bam, bam, bam.
It's weird.